Ryan Jamison

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Technical professional with a proven record of leadership amongst diverse individuals in a competitive business environment. Outgoing, personable, and able to adapt well in strenuous conditions. Innovative thinker with experience as a government contractor. Graduate of University of Pennsylvania Full Stack Developer Bootcamp. Motivated to bring background in entrepreneurship & technical skills ,to create unique and fluid full stack web applications.

DEMONSTRATED ACHIEVEMENTS

*Created Full Stack Web applications using the latest technologies
*Successfully ran campaign for
Committeeperson in 50th Ward
*Successfully completed accelerated developer bootcamp at the University of Pennsylvania

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Javascript, Node.js, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, MySQL, MongoDB, JQuery, Restful API, Git, RESTful API, Adobe Creative Suite.

CONTACT INFORMATION

Telephone: 215-290-5159

Email: ryanjamison26@gmail.com

LinkedIn: Ryan Jamison

GitHub: Rdj215 8561 Michener Ave., Philadelphia, PA 19150

PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

PRESIDENT - JAMISON CONTRACTING, LLC 2011-2019

- Position firm to compete for competitive bid contracts by building a visible brand through strategic partnerships, community outreach, and aggressive marketing.
- Work closely with high level officers throughout procurement process including but not limited to pre-bid meetings, site visits, proposals, and scheduling of work.
- Partner with nationally and regionally recognized entities including SEPTA, Amazon, Philadelphia Water, Philadelphia Job Corps, and Office of Senator Art Haywood.
- Oversee operations to ensure company initiatives and goals are met.
- Secure funding for operations, negotiate payment terms with vendors and clients.
- Participate in trainings/programs for small businesses

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA

Certificate - Full Stack Developer Bootcamp June 2019

INDIANA UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA

No Degree - Business Administration 2009

WALTER BIDDLE SAUL HS FOR AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES

Diploma - Landscape & Design 2007

OTHER EXPERIENCE

MAYOR'S COMMISSION ON AFRICAN AMERICAN MALES

2019 - Present Commission Member

50TH DEMOCRATIC WARD EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE

2018 - Present Committee Person

MILLENNIALS IN ACTION

2017 - 2019 Board Member

REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST